Okay, so what we're doing is we are checking our oil in our vehicle, and this is really important.
Oil, has been explained to me a few times, the lifeblood of your car and you obviously don't want that to go bad.
How often do you want to change your oil is a good question.
Generally most people say by 3,000 miles or 3 months, your oil sitting in your car, so that's a pretty good estimate, I mean, it kind of depends on your car, it depends on the oil.
But you definitely want to get your oil changed, you want to make sure you're changing it because it's really, really important.
So what we're going to do right now is check our oil, which is pretty straight forward.
Generally, most cars you'll find a dipstick with, for example, this one has a little oil graphic on it.
So what you're going to want to do is, you just pull this out, go ahead and wipe off the oil that's on there right now because the oil might have jumped up and down or it might have rubbed up against something, just to get a clean read.
So wipe it off first, you put it back in, make sure it goes all the way back in, and then pull it right back out, and there should be a level on there.
For example, this one looks a little low, there's a little place marker on this one that says "add" and "safe", so "safe" is going to be, obviously you're going to be good on your oil.
If it's below the "add" line, then obviously you want to go ahead and add some oil.
But for our purposes, we're going to go ahead and change the oil.
So that's just a good way to, you want to monitor this every once in a while, just to make sure that you've got enough oil in there, because if you have too little oil, that could really damage your car.
So, that's checking your oil, and next we're going to go into actually changing the oil.